thepajamacommute.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy

                               Privacy Policy
We have created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to your
privacy and the protection of your information.
Why did you receive an email from us?
If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as
someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving
information in the future ("opt-in"), or (b) you have registered or otherwise have an
existing relationship with us.
We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.
How we protect your privacy?
We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data
used by our system.
Sharing and Usage
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without
your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to
us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting
you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted
service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with
you.
How can you stop receiving email from us?
Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from
us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the
instructions at the end of any email.
If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be
sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to
mypajamacommute@gmail.com for review.
This Privacy Policy was last updated on July 1, 2014
.
